Nick Jenvey

UX/UI Designer

I am a digital product and user experience designer with an ambition to improve the lives of others through design. Solving problems while creating memorable and meaningful experiences. In the teams I have worked with, I have played a fundamental role in constructing the UI and engaging in interactive UX processes and research to inform our design designs and solutions.

Experience

Sprung Studios

UX/UI Designer October 2019 - October 2021

- Participated in UX design ideation sessions
- Performed UX research, referencing and competitive analysis to validate and confirm design decisions
- Constructed user and screen flows to better understand player's journeys
- Designed lo-fi wireframes and explored user experience solutions
- Created hi-fi designs and conducted formal presentation and feedback sessions with clients

Wine Works

Front-end Web Developer March 2017 - October 2018

- Responsible for development of both in-house and client provided designs
- Assessed clients sales objectives and tailored the UX to reflect those goals
- Became the first in-house designer and allowed the company to begin offering design services
- Designed visually appealing online store fronts that focused on ease of use and interactivity
- Produced comprehensive wireframe designs
- Honed my self-management skills by working remotely while staying on track with all projects



- □ nick@nickjenvey.com
- **(**604) 657-0627
- www.nickjenvey.com
- Vancouver, BC
- in /in/nickjenvey

Skills

- Creative and analytical thinking
- Attention to detail
- Collaboration
- Implementing and managing timelines
- UX research
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- UI design
- Usability testing
- Branding
- · Coding knowledge

Education

Lighthouse Labs

Web Development Diploma August 2019

BCIT

Senior Management Certificate October 2012

References available and provided upon request



Steady Studios

Web Designer

November 2015 - April 2017

- Designed UI that placed emphasis on human experience and increased brand awareness
- Worked with the development team to determine design solutions while working within their requirements
- Assisted branding team with various aspects of design projects (style guides, logo design, brochure design)

Novacode

Co-founder/Web Designer June 2015 - March 2017

- Responsible for creating all design assets from concept to final hand-off to development
- Worked with clients to define their vision and ensure all designs were inline with their needs and goals
- Managed client expectations and created timelines & work flows for development team
- Developed exceptional verbal & visual communication skills through working closely with clients
- Assisted the development team to complete projects with tight deadlines

Megacast

Visual Designer January 2013 - June 2016

- Created display advertisements and print brochures for marketing purposes
- Designed mobile responsive websites for companies in a multitude of industries
- Exposure to the fast-paced life of the agency environment
- Built lead generation landing pages and monitored page analytics to ensure goals were being met
- Participated in the creation of brand identities (logo creation, colour palette, print and web-based materials, and style guides)